[Music]
I'm ready when you are
I know it's fine I know but if it was
broke you would know oh yeah you're fine
it's cash so your pants are down it's
not believing this just cash
[Music]
daddy wasn't fine
thousands of people get hit by cars
every day but it takes a special kind of
idiot to hit himself with one that's
gentry and like most children half his
age he loves RC cars the minute you're
old enough to drive a real car you
should be donating all that crap to Toys
for Tots RC cars were invented so
father's could buy back the love of
their sons after a messy divorce as long
as you've got a massive stockpile of D
batteries and no shag carpet it can be
minutes of fun it's basically Mario Kart
for dorks who want to stand outside
while they get no exercise and that
controller also seals up every couch
within a half-mile range
why do they all have to look like sports
cars you're telling me there are no kids
out there who just want to buy a
reliable RC Toyota Camry that will get
their action figures from point A to
point B but who am I to tell anyone to
stop being childish
Gentry's fine he's fine that's why I
flew him to Hollywood where every guy
driving an exotic car is compensating
for his one-tenth scale weenie and this
week's web Redemption
[Applause]
[Music]
I live my life 1/100 of a mile at a time
why'd you bring me here Daniel I've one
more job I can't help you you know I'm
done racing toys you don't turn your
back on family we're not family that's
exactly what family would say brother
tell me what happened that day me and my
friends were out testing my speed car I
hit the gas at the wrong point and the
car just spun right around and before I
knew it I was upside down and on my ass
and knocked out all right did you ever
think of steering the car away from you
they come at you quite fast basically
it's like dodging bullets at this point
it would've been great if it would have
flipped you all the way back to your
feet oh I did make it awesome scorpion
now how fast was that car going when it
hit you 94 and that's legal to race
something around like that yeah first of
all your friends dead wrong you were not
fine dude your legs are fine yeah it was
not fine I got the indent on my leg
that's never gonna look good no over
here a part went into my leg that was a
puncture wound and I got sewn up and
stapled did he ever apologize hey I'm
sorry I miss diagnosed you you know is
he a paramedic no man shut up are you
still friends with him to this day yeah
he's here with me you brought him to my
garage you kept telling Gentry he was
fine I thought he was fine didn't you
use ii know how long we off your feet i
missed my first full week of work at my
new job and what did they say when you
said i the reason have to take off is
because i ran an RC car into my leg they
laugh they said we hired the right guy
did you post the video yeah were you
happy when people started watching it
people and YouTube are the meanest
people on the planet sexist racist bunch
of horrible people on YouTube ah I love
them love them all I get around what
happens if your car gets out of range it
stops
how far can they go before the unit
range 1100 to 1200 feet I've no idea how
far that is farther and you can see
that's not true I see the moon at night
farther than you can see something this
big you win that round
do you know what the world record speed
is for an RC car yeah its 202 are you
trying to beat that no that guy has
thousands upon thousands of dollars and
zero girlfriends how fast did your first
RC car go and how slow did your
virginity go after that did you get into
RC cars for all the have you ever
met a girl the plays with RC cars what
does your girlfriend I'm sorry your mom
think about the fact that you're still
playing with RC cars do girls like it
that you play with RC cars it's better
than doing drugs I guess not for girls
those love drugs
so one less ride you win I told you I'm
out baby there's a change your mind
what's this they took your girlfriend
look at that body you're a lucky man
here's the deal there's a huge battery
shipment going to RadioShack and we're
gonna hijack that truck sounds dangerous
with my RC car and your thumbs and your
mom's permission the only thing that can
stop us is our cars 15 minute battery
life fine but this is it I almost died
last time welcome back let's get to work
my first family barbecue it's 8:00 a.m.
and stop saying we're family when you're
here you're family
let's go for a little ride
it should be good for a ten-mile rage if
everything goes exactly as planned as
these things always do that truck should
be arriving any second
[Music]
Oh
suck it Hey
[Applause]
[Music]
- Hamlet
you're fine you're on fire I know but
you're fine
[Music]
I lost my family
if you like that Redemption good news
there will be 9 sequels
[Music]
[Applause]